Guide to the Arden B. Schell Watergate Collection, 1972-1974
George Mason University Libraries
- Arden B. Schell Watergate collection, 1972-1974
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (37.1 - 37.6), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    4.63
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (38.1), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    4.64
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    4.65 (Milk--Price supports for); Associated Milk Producers, Inc. (AMPI); Fred J. Buzhardt; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); John Dean; John Ehrlichman; H.R. Haldeman; Jacob Jacobsen; Herbert Kalmbach; Robert Lilly; George Mehren; Lee Nunn; Wall Street Journal; Washington Post; John Whitaker; Rose Mary Woods
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4 (39.1 - 39.4), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    4.66
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4 (40.1 - 40.5), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    4.67
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4 (41.1 - 41.6), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    4.68
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4 (42.1 - 42.6), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    4.69
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4 (43.1), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    4.70
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4 (44.1 - 44.3), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    4.71
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 4 (45.1 - 45.5), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    4.72
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    4.73 (Cambodia; wiretaps regarding Vietnam; wiretapping) Alexander Butterfield; John "Jack" Caulfield; Cartha DeLoach; C.F. Downing; John Ehrlichman; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Alexander Haig; H.R. Haldeman; Morton Halperin; J. Edgar Hoover; Courtland Jones; Herbert Kalmbach; Jim Keogh; Henry Kissinger; Joseph Kraft; Melvin Laird; Jeb Stuart Magruder; John N. Mitchell; Edmund Muskie (US Senate); National Security Council (wiretapping); Elliot Richardson; Republican National Committee; William Ruckelshaus; William Sullivan; Anthony Ulasewicz
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.8), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    4.74
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.6), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    4.75
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.4), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    4.76
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (4.1 - 4.4), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    4.77
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.2), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    4.78
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (6.1 - 6.5), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    4.79
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.5), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    4.80
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.5), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    4.81
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.3), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    4.82
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.6), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    4.83
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.4), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    4.84
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.4), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    4.85
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (13.1 - 13.5), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    4.86
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (14.1 - 14.3), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    4.87
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (15.1 - 15.3), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    5.1
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (16.1 - 16.7), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    5.2
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (17.1), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    5.3
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (18.1 - 18.6), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    5.4
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 1 (19.1 - 19.3), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    5.5
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    5.6 (Huston Plan; Domestic intelligence; Pentagon papers; US v. Russo; Domestic violence); Donald Bennett; John "Jack" Caulfield; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Dwight Chapin; John Dean; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); H.R. Haldeman; Richard Helms; J. Edgar Hoover; Thomas Charles Huston; Intelligence Evaluation Committee; Inter-Divisional Information Unit (IDIU); Interagency Committee on Intelligence; Herbert Kalmbach; Edward M. Kennedy (US Senate); Henry Kissinger; John N. Mitchell; National Security Agency; New York Times; Donald Nixon; Donald Segretti; Senate Armed Services Committee; John Sparkman (US Senate); Gordon Strachan; Washington Post
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (20.1 - 20.5), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    5.7
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (21.1 - 51.5), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    5.8
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (22.1 - 22.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    5.9
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (23.1 - 23.7), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    5.10
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (24.1 - 24.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    5.11
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (25.1 - 25.8), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    5.12
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (26.1 - 26.7), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    5.13
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (27.1 - 27.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    5.14
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (28.1 - 28.2), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    5.15
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (29.1 - 29.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    5.16
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (30.1 - 30.7), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    5.17
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (31.1 - 31.5), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    5.18
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (32.1 - 32.2), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    5.19
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (33.1 - 33.6), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    5.20
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (34.1 - 34.2), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    5.21
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 2 (35.1 - 35.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    5.22
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    5.23 (Pentagon papers; San Clemente, California); Brookings Institution; Patrick Buchanan; John "Jack" Caulfield; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Charles Colson; Robert Cushman; Clifton DeMotte; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); H.R. Haldeman; Morton Halperin; Howard E. Hunt; Edward M. Kennedy (US Senate); Henry Kissinger; Egil Krogh; George Gordon Liddy; Robert Mardian; Donald Stewart; William Sullivan; White House special investigation unit ("Plumbers"); David Young
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (36.1), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    5.24
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (37.1 - 37.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    5.25
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (38.1 - 38.4), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    5.26
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (39.1 - 39.2), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    5.27
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (40.1 - 40.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    5.28
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (41.1 - 41.7), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    5.29
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (42.1 - 42.5), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    5.30
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (43.1 - 43.4), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    5.31
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (44.1 - 44.4), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    5.32
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (45.1 - 45.3), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    5.33
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (46.1 - 46.2), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    5.34
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (47.1 - 47.5), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    5.35
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (48.1 - 48.4), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    5.36
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (49.1), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    5.37
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (50.1 - 51.7), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    5.38
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (51.1 - 51.6), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    5.39
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (52.1 - 52.2), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    5.40
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (53.1 - 53.4), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    5.41
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (54.1 - 54.4), 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    5.42
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 3 (55.1 - 55.6), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    5.43
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    5.44 (Pentagon papers; Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty (SALT); Vietnam; wiretapping); Bernard Barker; Leonard Boudin; CBS News; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Charles Colson; Lucian Conein; Felipe de Diego; Ngo Dinh Diem; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Lewis Fielding; Patrick Gray; Alexander Haig; H.R. Haldeman; J. Edgar Hoover; Howard E. Hunt; John F. Kennedy; Henry Kissinger; Joseph Kraft; Egil Krogh; William Lambert; George Gordon Liddy; Robert Mardian; Eugenio Martinez; Daniel Schorr; William Sullivan; White House special investigation unit ("Plumbers"); David Young
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (56.1 - 56.6), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    5.45
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (57.1 - 57.7), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    5.46
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (58.1 - 58.4), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    5.47
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (59.1 - 59.5), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    5.48
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (60.1), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    5.49
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (61.1 - 61.6), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    5.50
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (62.1 - 62.11), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    5.51
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (63.1 - 63.3), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    5.52
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (64.1 - 64.4), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    5.53
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (65.1 - 65.4), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    5.54
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 4 (66.1 - 66.6), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    5.55
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    5.56 (Cape Cod, Massachusetts; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; India-Pakistan War; "Plumbers" Unit; "Sandwedge" Operation; wiretapping); Bernard Barker; Joseph Baroody; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Dwight Chapin; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); Robert Cushman; Felipe de Diego; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Lewis Fielding; Richard Helms; Hubert Humphrey; Howard E. Hunt; Egil Krogh; George Gordon Liddy; Eugenio Martinez; George McGovern; Edmund Muskie (US Senate); National Security Council; Donald Segretti; Washington Post; David Young
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (67.1 - 67.7), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    5.57
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (68.1 - 68.5), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    5.58
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (69.1 - 69.4), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    5.59
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (70.1 - 70.4), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    5.60
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (71.1 - 71.8), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    5.61
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (72.1 - 72.6), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    5.62
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (73.1 - 73.5), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    5.63
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (74.1 - 74.3), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    5.64
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (75.1 - 75.10), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    5.65
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (76.1 - 76.7), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    5.66
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (77.1), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    5.67
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (78.1 - 78.4), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    5.68
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (79.1 - 79.6), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    5.69
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (80.1), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    5.70
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 5 (81.1 - 81.2), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    5.71
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    5.72 (Miami, Florida; Pentagon papers); Bernard Barker; Dwight Chapin; Cathleen Chenow; John Dean; Democratic National Committee (DNC); Daniel Ellsberg; Fred Fielding; Lewis Fielding; H.R. Haldeman; Howard E. Hunt; Egil Krogh; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Robert Mardian; Eugenio Martinez; John N. Mitchell; Henry Peterson; Donald Segretti; Earl Silbert; Washington Post
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (82.1), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    5.73
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (83.1 - 83.5), 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    5.74
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (84.1 - 84.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    5.75
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (85.1 - 85.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    5.76
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (86.1 - 86.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    5.77
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (87.1 - 87.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    5.78
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (88.1 - 88.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    5.79
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (89.1 - 89.5), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    5.80
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (90.1 - 90.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    5.81
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (91.1 - 91.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    5.82
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (92.1 - 92.6), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    5.83
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (93.1 - 93.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    5.84
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (94.1 - 94.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    5.85
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (95.1 - 95.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    5.86
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 6 (96.1 - 96.6), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    5.87
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    6.1 (Key Biscayne, Florida; Pentagon papers; "Plumbers" Unit; San Clemente, California; wiretapping); William Matthew Byrne, Jr.; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Dwight Chapin; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); Robert Cushman; John Dean; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Mark Felt; Lewis Fielding; Patrick Gray; Howard E. Hunt; Herbert Kalmbach; Richard Kleindienst; Egil Krogh; George Gordon Liddy; Richard Moore; New York Times; Henry Peterson; James Schlessinger; Donald Segretti; William Sullivan; Time Magazine; White House special investigation unit ("Plumbers"); Ronald Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (97.1), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    6.2
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (98.1 - 98.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    6.3
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (99.1 - 99.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    6.4
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (100.1 - 100.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    6.5
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (101.1 - 101.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    6.6
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (102.1), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    6.7
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (103.1 - 103.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    6.8
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (104.1 - 104.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    6.9
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (105.1), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    6.10
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (106.1 - 106.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    6.11
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (107.1 - 107.7), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    6.12
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (108.1), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    6.13
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (109.1 - 109.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    6.14
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (110.1 - 110.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    6.15
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (111.1), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    6.16
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (112.1 - 112.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    6.17
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (113.1 - 113.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    6.18
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 7 (114.1 - 114.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    6.19
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    6.20 William Matthew Byrne, Jr.; Dwight Chapin; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg (wiretapping); Seymour Glanzer; Morton Halperin; J. Edgar Hoover; Howard E. Hunt; Joseph Kraft; George Gordon Liddy; Richard Moore; David Nissen; Henry Peterson; William Rogers; William Ruckelshaus; Donald Segretti; Earl Silbert; Washington Star News; David Young
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (115.1 - 115.4), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    6.21
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (116.1 - 116.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    6.22
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (117.1 - 117.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    6.23
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (118.1 - 118.3), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    6.24
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (119.1 - 119.6), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    6.25
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (120.1), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    6.26
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (121.1), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    6.27
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (122.1 - 122.6), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    6.28
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (123.1 - 123.2), 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    6.29
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (124.1 - 124.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    6.30
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (125.1 - 125.4), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    6.31
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (126.1 - 126.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    6.32
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (127.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    6.33
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (128.1 - 128.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    6.34
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (129.1 - 129.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    6.35
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (130.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    6.36
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (131.1 - 131.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    6.37
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (132.1 - 132.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    6.38
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (133.1 - 133.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    6.39
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    6.40 ("Enemies" list; "Opponents" list) Vernon Acree; Brookings Institution; John "Jack" Caulfield; Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); John Dean; Lawrence Goldberg; Billy Graham; Robert Greene; H.R. Haldeman; Lawrence Higby; Thomas Charles Huston; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Egil Krogh; Clark Mollenhoff; Newsday; C.G. Rebozo; Randolph Thrower; Treasury Department; Charles Walker; George Wallace; Washington Post; John Wayne
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.4), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    6.41
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (2.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    6.42
  - Evidentiary Notebook 7, Vol. 8 (3.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    6.43
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (4.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    6.44
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.12), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    6.45
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (6.1 - 6.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    6.46
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    6.47
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    6.48
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.8), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    6.49
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    6.50
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    6.51
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    6.52
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (13.1 - 13.6), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    6.53
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 1 (14.1 + 14.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    6.54
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    6.55 ("Enemies" list; "Millhouse: A White Comedy"; "Sandwedge" Operation); Roger Barth; Fred J. Buzhardt; John "Jack" Caulfield; Center on Corporate Responsibility, Inc.; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); John Dean; Emile Deantonio; Democratic National Committee (DNC) (Staff tax investigation by IRS); John Ehrlichman; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI); Harold Gibbons; H.R. Haldeman; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Herbert Kalmbach; George Gordon Liddy; New Yorker Films; Lawrence F. O'Brien (income tax returns); James Polk; George Schultz; Gordon Strachan; Daniel Talbot; Teamsters; Fred Thompson; Anthony Ulasewicz; Johnnie Walters
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (15.1 - 15.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    6.56
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (16.1 - 16.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    6.57
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (17.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    6.58
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (18.1 - 18.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    6.59
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (19.1 - 19.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    6.60
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (20.1 - 20.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    6.61
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (21.1 - 21.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    6.62
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (22.1 - 22.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    6.63
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (23.1 - 23.3), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    6.64
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (24.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    6.65
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (25.1 - 25.7), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    6.66
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (26.1 - 26.2), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    6.67
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (27.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    6.68
  - Evidentiary Notebook 8, Vol. 2 (28.1), 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    6.69
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    6.70 (San Clemente, California; Watergate Special Prosecutor appointment; White House taping system); American Airlines Corp. (contributions to CRP); Alexander Butterfield; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); Archibald Cox; John Ehrlichman (Resignation); Ervin Committee; Sam Ervin (US Senate); Fred Fielding; Alexander Haig; H.R. Haldeman (resignation); International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Richard Kleindienst (resignation); Fred Larue; Elliot Richardson (nomination to Attorney General); Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.6), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    6.71
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    6.72
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.4), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    6.73
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (4.1 - 4.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    6.74
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    6.75
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (6.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    6.76
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    6.77
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    6.78
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.6), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    6.79
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.5), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    6.80
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    6.81
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    6.82
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (13.1 - 13.5), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    6.83
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (14.1 - 14.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    6.84
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (14a.1 -14a.6), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    6.85
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (15.1 - 15.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    6.86
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (16.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    6.87
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (17.1 - 17.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    6.88
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (18.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    6.89